<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog
        https://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-latest.xsd">

    <changeSet id="1723793544028-1.1.1" author="jason.zhuang" dbms="postgresql">
        <preConditions onFail="MARK_RAN"  onError="MARK_RAN">
            <sqlCheck expectedResult="0">
                SELECT COUNT(*) FROM information_schema.tables WHERE table_name = 'articles';
            </sqlCheck>
        </preConditions>
        <sql>
            CREATE TABLE spring."articles"
            (
                "id"             INTEGER GENERATED BY DEFAULT AS IDENTITY (START WITH 11) NOT NULL,
                "title"          VARCHAR(255)                                             NOT NULL,
                "content"        TEXT                                                     NOT NULL,
                "author"         VARCHAR(100),
                "published_date" TIMESTAMP WITHOUT TIME ZONE DEFAULT NOW(),
                "is_published"   BOOLEAN                     DEFAULT FALSE,
                CONSTRAINT "articles_pkey" PRIMARY KEY ("id")
            );
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="1723793544028-1.1.2" author="jason.zhuang" dbms="postgresql">
        <preConditions onFail="MARK_RAN" onError="MARK_RAN">
            <sqlCheck expectedResult="0">
                SELECT COUNT(*) FROM spring.articles;
            </sqlCheck>
        </preConditions>
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO spring.articles (title, content, author, published_date, is_published)
            VALUES
                ('The Future of Artificial Intelligence', 'Artificial Intelligence is rapidly evolving, with advancements in machine learning and deep learning pushing the boundaries of what is possible. In this article, we explore the potential future developments and their impact on various industries.', 'Jane Doe', '2024-08-01 10:00:00', TRUE),

                ('Understanding Quantum Computing', 'Quantum computing promises to revolutionize the field of computing by solving complex problems much faster than classical computers. This article provides an overview of quantum computing principles and their potential applications.', 'John Smith', '2024-08-05 14:30:00', TRUE),

                ('The Evolution of Web Development', 'Web development has come a long way since the early days of HTML and CSS. We discuss the evolution of web technologies, from static pages to dynamic web applications, and what the future holds for web development.', 'Emily Johnson', '2024-08-10 09:45:00', TRUE),

                ('Climate Change and Its Global Effects', 'Climate change is one of the most pressing issues of our time. This article examines the global effects of climate change, including rising sea levels, extreme weather events, and impacts on biodiversity.', 'Michael Brown', '2024-08-12 16:00:00', TRUE),

                ('The Rise of Remote Work', 'Remote work has become increasingly popular, especially in the wake of the COVID-19 pandemic. We explore the benefits and challenges of remote work and its long-term implications for the future of work.', 'Sara Davis', '2024-08-15 11:20:00', TRUE),

                ('Exploring Space Tourism', 'Space tourism is an exciting frontier in the travel industry. This article delves into the current state of space tourism, key players in the industry, and what future space travelers can expect.', 'Robert Wilson', '2024-08-20 13:10:00', TRUE),

                ('Advancements in Renewable Energy', 'Renewable energy sources are critical to reducing our carbon footprint. We highlight recent advancements in solar, wind, and hydro energy technologies and their impact on the energy sector.', 'Linda Miller', '2024-08-22 15:00:00', TRUE),

                ('The Importance of Mental Health Awareness', 'Mental health awareness is crucial for reducing stigma and providing support. This article discusses the importance of mental health awareness and ways to promote mental well-being in communities.', 'David Martinez', '2024-08-25 08:30:00', TRUE),

                ('The Impact of Social Media on Society', 'Social media has a profound impact on society, influencing everything from communication to politics. We analyze the positive and negative effects of social media on modern life.', 'Rachel Anderson', '2024-08-28 12:00:00', TRUE),

                ('Trends in Mobile App Development', 'Mobile app development continues to evolve with new technologies and user expectations. This article reviews the latest trends in mobile app development and what developers should focus on.', 'James Lee', '2024-08-30 17:45:00', TRUE);
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>